[{"answer": "Absolute tragedy, Piers.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Do you condemn them?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "I think unfortunately it's going to put more fuel on the fire that was already lit today.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Would you condemn them for calling for those protests?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, think all too often extremists on both sides, the violent extremists that did the attack today, the extremists down in Florida, Terry Jones, control this conversation.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Where will this end, do you think, Corey?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, the government is the government here is dismissing out of hand, it seems, the conditional cease-fire that the opposition has put forward.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What is the latest?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "He feels he has.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Is that accurate, do you think?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Nic, thank you very much.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Are they going to continue them at the level they have been at, serious and aggressive, or are they going to start to back off?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, if you talk to government officials like we've been doing in Yemen, many have already written the President Saleh's political obituary.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "How long has he got?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I think what he did was certainly unnecessary and I think the consequences have been horrific.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Would you blame Mr. Jones for what happened today?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, you want him not to do things like that.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "I mean, there's got to be some way of stopping people like Terry Jones behaving this way, isn't there?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, honestly, Piers, I do think that it is time for the other countries in NATO and the Arab League to take more charge here, to take more responsibility.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Is it a sensible time for America to be withdrawing?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Give me a ballpark.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know that one has anything to do with the other.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Why don't you just give them some money?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, I will not carry on shooting elephants.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Will you carry on shooting elephants then?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, ever since this oafish violent video posted, we have taken our business with GoDaddy and gone elsewhere.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I disagree with that totally.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Let me tell you about the smile I have on my face at that time.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "If you were doing for this some kind of humanitarian purpose, why are you looking like you're some kind of super hunter with your kill there?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "He's killed other wild animals.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "And any other animals?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "No, none at all.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Have you had any financial damage to your company, GoDaddy.com, so far, in light this incident?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "And I'll tell you why -- because most people -- most Americans understand people need to eat.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "So, nobody's removed any money?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "You seem relatively harmless, but all the best serial killers are harmless to look at.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Do I seem dangerous to you?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "ILVERMAN: I just go by a guideline of -- if it makes my heart sink or it makes me feel bad, then I won't say it.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Where are your limits?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "But don't all comedians want attention?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Of course!", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "To hang out with you?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "No, you're a lot of fun.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Why wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Oh, my God.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "What are you fears?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Rather.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "What should we talk about?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I would love to make you cry.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "I mean, what do you want?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "But only if it helps you, ultimately, if it is some sort of breakthrough.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "You want to?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "You're quite bolshy.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Are you playful?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "It depends on the situation.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Or is it like an undercurrent of menace?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Right now, I'm feeling --", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "How you feeling at the moment?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "No, he's an actor named John Hamm.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Isn't he?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Right, yes.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "The types who are in these shows are fairly ghastly, aren't they?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I understood that.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "What are you looking at?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "That's what I hear.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Sorry?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "You hear doit-doit-doit?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "It's all the same, isn't it?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Touche.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "It's all the same, isn't it?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Touche is a French word.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Is that a British word?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Oh, because France is basically Britain, right?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Doit, doit, doit, doit.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Across the pond?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I love America.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "What your view of your great country?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "That is such a weird question.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "You think America loves you?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I shouldn't think so for a moment, no.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Do you think America loves you?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I think when you talk about a whole people, it's--", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "They probably think who is obnoxious little Limey Brit we have got sitting here?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "--getting, you are generalizing a bit.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "How about the great Larry King?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I'm popular for a Jew.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "No, I mean, does it matter to you that you are popular in America?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Uh, is it not?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "But there is outrage when he said things like that.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "I mean, I think when stuff like Mel Gibson, when he said, like, you know, like Jewish stuff or anything like that?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "You were very candid in that book.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "And beautiful and perfect, and it would be true, you know?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Can you be a successful, smart comedian, without having gone through a lot of crap in your life?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I don't know!", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "No, I mean, you know-yeah, no!", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Because your family was-it wasn't a misery scenario was it?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Was it the divorce do you think?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "ORGAN: From the most unlikely background.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Because what did I have to loose?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I had nothing to loose.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Is that what you felt?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Uh, nothing.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "What would you like from your life that you don't have?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "They don't have to be comedians but they have to be funny.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "You have an allergy to non-funny people, don't you?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Oooh, I think that make me laugh, but both.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Do you prefer men that make you laugh, or who laugh at your jokes?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "ILVERMAN: So weird.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "You are such weird people, aren't you, comedians?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "We're talking to people who make responsibility for other people's happiness.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "You know what I mean?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Oy!?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Yeah!", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Do you still feel as passionate about him as you did then?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "You mother (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Ugh!", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Can we fast forward to the bit where you make a complete ass of yourself?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "There is-ugh.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Didn't you then inform him that in your next movie you were going to be nude?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, he goes, \"Well, what's next for you?\"", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Can we just have the exact wording?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "He defused the situation, you know, generously like-", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "He said it not in a pervy way.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "He didn't say that?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "But in a let's make her not feel weird by saying a weird thing.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "What other way can it not be pervy?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "It was levity.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "The president of the United States immediately responded by asking if you could send him a copy of the movie in which you are naked?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Well, no, because I know what it is.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Were you flattered that the president wanted to see you naked?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Michelle was in hearing distance?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "They're completely different.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "And standout, where you walk out, it's live, it's all whatever you want to do, and then it's all over?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "It is one of those botched names, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "Kate.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "What is your middle name?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "Give me a break.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "I wish I could say it's been a pleasure, but it's been tense, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "I'm saying only me.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Should nobody be searched?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Because of who I am.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Why just you?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "You believe in profiling, basically?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110401pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "Would you only profile Muslims at airports?", "qSentId": 829}]